通过这个文档，我们需要的是单选模式
From the documentation, we want singleChoice, mode so
这样可以保证同一时刻只有一个列表项显示被选中
that the list item only shows one selected item at a time.
你可以在fragment_main布局中的listview控件里声明这个属性
You can declare this attribute on the list view in the fragment_main file.
然而，我们并不希望在单一屏幕模式时指定选择模式
However, we don't want to specify ChoiceMode in one ping mode. So, to
所以，为了可以有不同的代码路径，我们把这个布局文件复制到
have these different code paths, we could copy the file in the Layout folder and
Layout-sw600dp文件夹中
put it in the Layout and put it in the Layout-sw600dp folder.
更好的解决方案是声明一个style，这样，我们只有一个布局文件
A better solution is to declare a style. So, we have one layout file but
但拥有不同的style.在values文件夹中的Base style 文件里
different styles. In the Base styles file in the values folder,
我们声明一个ForecastListStyle。先让它空着就可以
we declare ForecastListStyle. We leave it empty because we don't need to
因为还不需要指定选择模式。在Layout-sw600dp文件夹里创建一个新的style文件
specify ChoiceMode. We create a new styles file in the values-sw600dp folder.
这两种情况下，ForecastListStyle包含了选择模式
In the two pane case, the ForecastListStyle does include the ChoiceMode.
这两个文件有不同数量的style。如果不是声明在更高层级的文件夹里
The two files have a different number of styles. If it's not declared in
它会退回基本style
a higher folder, then it will just fall back to the Base style.